A Guide to the Papers of Emily Couric, ca. 1983-2002
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II: Campaign Materials
  - Subseries A: 1995 Campaign
    - Media- Postcards and Bumper Stickers, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 48:4)
    - Media- Press Releases, 1995 (Box-folder 48:5)
    - Media - Transcripts- WWWV and WINA, 1995 July 16, 21 (Box-folder 48:6)
    - Media- Television and Filming, 1994 August (Box-folder 48:7)
    - Media- Television and Radio Spots, 1995 (Box-folder 48:8)
    - Media- Yard Signs, 1994, 1995 (Box-folder 48:9)
    - National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL), 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 48:10)
    - Newspaper Articles, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 48:11)
    - Opponents- Donal Day, 1995 (Box-folder 48:12)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- 1991 Campaign, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 48:13)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- 1995 Race, 1993-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 48:14)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Absences, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 48:15)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Attack Mail, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 48:16)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Education Fact Kit, 1995, August (Box-folder 48:17)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Finance Reports- Contributions and Expenditures, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Finance Reports- Contributions and Expenditures, 1993-1995 (Box-folder 49:2)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Finance Reports- Receipts and Disbursements, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 49:3)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Finance Reports- Tom Michie, 1991 (Box-folder 49:4)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Hit and Run, 1993 (Box-folder 49:5)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Personal, 1988-1997 (Box-folder 49:6)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Research Report, 1995 May (Box-folder 49:7)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Schewel Letter, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 49:8)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Speeches, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 49:9)
    - Opponents- Ed Robb- Statement of Economic Interest, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 49:10)
    - Opponents- Eric Strzepek, 1995 (Box-folder 49:11)
    - Personal Record- School Board Attendance, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 49:12)
    - Polling, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 49:13)
    - Polling- Precinct Coordination, 1995 (Box-folder 50:1)
    - Polling- Tabular Report #627, 1995 October (Box-folder 50:2)
    - Polling- Tabular Report #629, 1995 October (Box-folder 50:3)
    - Questionnaires- AFL- CIO, 1995 June (Box-folder 50:4)
    - Questionnaires- Chamber of Commerce, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 50:5)
    - Questionnaires- Clean Water Action/Virginia Vote Environment, 1995 (Box-folder 50:6)
    - Questionnaires- Coalition for Mentally Disabled Citizens of Virginia, 1995 September (Box-folder 50:7)
    - Questionnaires- Community Rehabilitation Programs, 1995 (Box-folder 50:8)
    - Questionnaires- Greene County Record, 1995 (Box-folder 50:9)
    - Questionnaires- Human Services Association Political Action Committee, 1995 (Box-folder 50:10)
    - Questionnaires- League of Women Voters, 1995 (Box-folder 50:11)
    - Questionnaires- Make Women Count, 1995 (Box-folder 50:12)
    - Questionnaires- Tom Michie, 1991 (Box-folder 50:13)
    - Questionnaires- National Rifle Association- Handgun Control, 1995 (Box-folder 50:14)
    - Questionnaires- Not Returned, 1995 (Box-folder 50:15)
    - Questionnaires- Planned Parenthood, 1995 October (Box-folder 50:16)
    - Questionnaires- Richmond Times Dispatch,1995 October (Box-folder 50:17)
    - Questionnaires- Right to Work, 1995 August (Box-folder 50:18)
    - Questionnaires- Sierra Club, 1995 (Box-folder 50:19)
    - Questionnaires- Social Workers, 1995 (Box-folder 50:20)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Conservation Network, 1995 (Box-folder 50:21)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Education Association, 1995 (Box-folder 50:22)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Foundation for Research and Economic Education, 1995 (Box-folder 50:23)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Government Employees Association, 1995 (Box-folder 50:24)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Medical Political Action Committee, 1995 (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL), 1995 (Box-folder 51:2)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia National Organization for Women, 1995 (Box-folder 51:3)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia National Women's Political Caucus, 1995 (Box-folder 51:4)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Trial Lawyers Political Action Committee, 1995 (Box-folder 51:5)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians Deserve Better, 1995 (Box-folder 51:6)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians for Health Care Solutions, 1995 (Box-folder 51:7)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians for Justice, 1995 (Box-folder 51:8)
    - Questionnaires- Women's Campaign Fund, 1995 (Box-folder 51:9)
    - Rubber Stamps and Campaign Button, n.d. (Oversize 51)
    - Scrapbook- Campaign 1995, 1995 (Oversize 51)
  - Subseries B: 1999 Campaign
    - Administrative- Banquet License, n.d. (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Administrative- Bulk Mail, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 51:2)
    - Administrative- Campaign Budget, 1999 (Box-folder 51:3)
    - Administrative- Campaign Deadlines, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 51:4)
    - Administrative- Campaign Regulations, 1995 (Box-folder 51:5)
    - Administrative- Campaign Staff, 1996, 1999 (Box-folder 51:6)
    - Administrative- Catering Ideas, 1998 (Box-folder 51:7)
    - Administrative- Forest Lakes Residential Directory, n.d. (Box-folder 51:8)
    - Administrative- Greene County, 1999 (Box-folder 51:9)
    - Administrative- Hardware and Office Equipment, 1999 (Box-folder 51:10)
    - Administrative- Horizon Institute for Policy Solutions, 1999 (Box-folder 51:11)
    - Administrative- Important Information for 1999 Campaign, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 51:12)
    - Administrative- Important Information for 1999 Campaign, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 51:13)
    - Administrative- Membership Directories, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 52:1)
    - Administrative- Meet and Greets, 1998 (Box-folder 52:2)
    - Administrative- Parent Teacher Organizations/Schools, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 52:3)
    - Administrative- Phone Banks, 1999 October 25-26 (Box-folder 52:4)
    - Administrative- Phone Banks, 1999 October 26-29 (Box-folder 52:5)
    - Administrative- Polling, 1999 (Box-folder 52:6)
    - Administrative- Polling Tabular Report #1001, 1999 May (Box-folder 52:7)
    - Administrative- Polling Tabular Reports #1004, 1054, 1999 September-October (Box-folder 52:8)
    - Administrative- Pollsters- Cooper and Secrest, 1999 April 23 (Box-folder 52:9)
    - Administrative- Precinct Organization, 1999 (Box-folder 52:10)
    - Administrative- Taxes, 1999 (Box-folder 53:1)
    - Administrative- Volunteers, 1999 (Box-folder 53:2)
    - Administrative- Voter Registration, 1999 (Box-folder 53:3)
    - Appearances/Debates- Forums and Joint Appearances, 1995, 1999 (Box-folder 53:4)
    - Appearances/Debates- Kick-Off Swing, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 53:5)
    - Appearances/Debates- Debate Prep (1 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 53:6)
    - Appearances/Debates- Debate Prep (2 of 2), 1999 (Box-folder 53:7)
    - Appearances/Debates- Transcripts, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 53:8)
    - Candidates- Doris Lackey for Delegate, 1999 (Box-folder 53:9)
    - Candidates- Jody Wagner- Congressional Campaign, 2000 (Box-folder 53:10)
    - Candidates- Denise Oppenhagen, 1999 (Box-folder 53:11)
    - Candidates- Senate/House Races, 1999 (Box-folder 53:12)
    - Candidates- Eric Strucko for Supervisor, 1999 (Box-folder 53:13)
    - Candidates- Ed Wayland for Delegate, 1999 (Box-folder 53:14)
    - Financial- 2000 Democratic State Convention Charges (Marriott), 2000 (Box-folder 54:1)
    - Financial- Budget, 1999 (Box-folder 54:2)
    - Financial- Bulk Mail Account (Mail Services of Virginia), 1999 (Box-folder 54:3)
    - Financial- Campaign Financial Disclosure, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 54:4)
    - Financial- Disclosure Reports, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 54:5)
    - Financial- Disclosure Reports, 1999 (Box-folder 54:6)
    - Financial- Disclosure Reports- Correspondence, 1999 (Box-folder 54:7)
    - Financial- Expenditures, 2000 April-December (Box-folder 54:8)
    - Financial- Insurance, 1999 (Box-folder 54:9)
    - Financial- Invoices- Blue Ridge Graphics, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 54:10)
    - Financial- Invoices- Mary Broz, 2000 (Box-folder 54:11)
    - Financial- Invoices- Chase Bank Credit Card, 2000, n.d. (Box-folder 54:12)
    - Financial- Invoices Due, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 54:13)
    - Financial- Invoices- ESI Productions, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 54:14)
    - Financial- Invoices- FedEx, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 54:15)
    - Financial- Invoices- Hampton Inn and Suites- Standing Account, 2000 (Box-folder 54:16)
    - Financial- Invoices- IKON (Formerly Copy Cat), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 54:17)
    - Financial- Invoices- Johnny Howard Printing, 2000 (Box-folder 54:18)
    - Financial- Invoices- Kaminer and Thomson, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 54:19)
    - Financial- Invoices- Miscellaneous, 2000 (Box-folder 54:20)
    - Financial- Invoices- Papercraft Printing and Design, 1999 (Box-folder 55:1)
    - Financial- Invoices- Pixels, 1999 (Box-folder 55:2)
    - Financial- Invoices- T & N Printing, 1999 (Box-folder 55:3)
    - Financial- Invoices- Sir Speedy Printing, 1999 (Box-folder 55:4)
    - Financial- Invoices-Telephone (AT & T, MCI), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 55:5)
    - Financial- Invoices- Telephone (Sprint), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 55:6)
    - Financial- Invoices- Television and Radio Production, 1999 (Box-folder 55:7)
    - Financial- Office Space, 2000 (Box-folder 55:8)
    - Financial- Payroll Taxes, 2000 (Box-folder 55:9)
    - Financial- Reports, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 55:10)
    - Financial- Reports- Contributions and Expenditures, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 55:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Barboursville Event, 1999, 1 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 55:12)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Barboursville Event, 1999, 2 of 2 folders. (Box-folder 55:13)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Business Breakfast, 1999 (Box-folder 56:1)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Business Breakfast, 1999 (Box-folder 56:2)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Claiborne's, 1999 (Box-folder 56:3)
    - Fundraisers and Events - Claiborne's List, 1999 (Box-folder 56:4)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Claiborne's List, 1999 (Box-folder 56:5)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Family Fun Day 1998, 1998 (Box-folder 56:6)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Family Fun Day 1999, 1999 (Box-folder 56:7)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Fridays After 5, 1999 (Box-folder 57:1)
    - Fundraisers and Events- General, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 57:2)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Greencroft Women's Luncheon and Forum, 1999 (Box-folder 57:3)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Grisham Gala, 1998, 1 of 2. (Box-folder 57:4)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Grisham Gala, 1998, 2 of 2. (Box-folder 57:5)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Kassell Event, 1998 (Box-folder 57:6)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Kick-Off, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 57:7)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Lipper Party, n.d. (Box-folder 57:8)
    - Fundraisers and Events- LiveArts, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 57:9)
    - Fundraisers and Events- LiveArts Invite List, 1998 (Box-folder 57:10)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Madison/Rice Reception, 1999 (Box-folder 57:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events-Medical Society Fundraiser, 1995, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 57:12)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Nelson/Dolan Event, 1999 (Box-folder 58:1)
    - Fundraisers and Events- New Fundraising, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 58:2)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Nurses for Couric, 1999 (Box-folder 58:3)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Piedmont Defense Fund, n.d. (Box-folder 58:4)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Potential List Ideas, 1998 (Box-folder 58:5)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Redlands Fundraiser, 1999 (Box-folder 58:6)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Richmond Event, 1999 (Box-folder 58:7)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Sheras Mental Health Event, 1999 (Box-folder 58:8)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Solicitation Letter, 1999 (Box-folder 58:9)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Turner Fundraiser, 1998 (Box-folder 58:10)
    - Fundraisers and Events-Train Station Event, 1999 (Box-folder 58:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Venable Fundraiser, 1994, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 58:12)
    - Issues- Education Blueprint, 1999 (Box-folder 59:1)
    - Issues- General, 1999 (Box-folder 59:2)
    - Issues- Party Names on Ballots, 1999 (Box-folder 59:3)
    - Issues- Planned Parenthood, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 59:4)
    - Issues- Public Education in America: an Introduction, 1999, 1 of 2. (Box-folder 59:5)
    - Issues- Public Education in America: an Introduction, 1999, 2 of 2. (Box-folder 59:6)
    - Issues- Public Education in America: an Introduction- Associated Materials, 1999 (Box-folder 59:7)
    - Media- Albemarle Education Postcard, n.d. (Box-folder 59:8)
    - Media- Campaign Information, 1999 (Box-folder 59:9)
    - Media- Cavalier Daily Retraction, 1999 (Box-folder 59:10)
    - Media- Charlottesville Mailers, 1999 (Box-folder 59:11)
    - Media- Check the Record Postcard, 1999 (Box-folder 59:12)
    - Media- Direct Mail Samples, 1999 (Box-folder 59:13)
    - Media- Football Ads (Box-folder 59:14)
    - Media- Football Programs, 1999 (Box-folder 59:15)
    - Media- Earl Hammer- Radio Ad, 1999 (Box-folder 59:16)
    - Media- Joint Campaign Postcard, 1999 (Box-folder 59:17)
    - Media- Lackey/Couric Postcard, 1999 (Box-folder 59:18)
    - Media- Newsletter Outreach, 1998 (Box-folder 59:19)
    - Media- Outreach Ideas, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 59:20)
    - Media- Paid Media- David Doak, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 59:21)
    - Media- Palm Cards, 1999 (Box-folder 60:1)
    - Media- Positive Bio Mailer, 1999 (Box-folder 60:2)
    - Media- Postcards, 1999 (Box-folder 60:3)
    - Media- Press Releases, 1999 (Box-folder 60:4)
    - Media- Press Packet, 1999 (Box-folder 60:5)
    - Media- Printing, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 60:6)
    - Media- Website, 1995, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 60:7)
    - Past Election Results, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 60:8)
    - Personal Legislative Record, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 60:9)
    - Politics- Darden, 1999 November 1 (Box-folder 60:10)
    - Politics- Democratic Caucus, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 60:11)
    - Politics- Democratic Caucus- Confidential Caucus Material, 1999 (Box-folder 60:12)
    - Politics- Democratic Caucus- Mass Meeting Nominations, 1992, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 60:13)
    - Politics- Democratic Party Calls, n.d. (Box-folder 60:14)
    - Politics- Farmington Country Club Membership List, 1995, July (Box-folder 60:15)
    - Politics- Republican Party, 1999 (Box-folder 60:16)
    - Positions Report, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 60:17)
    - Questionnaires- AFL- CIO, 1999 (Box-folder 61:1)
    - Questionnaires- Agribusiness Council/ Farm Bureau, 1999 (Box-folder 61:2)
    - Questionnaires- Charlottesville Area Association of Realtors, 1999 (Box-folder 61:3)
    - Questionnaires- Conservation Land Coalition, 1999 (Box-folder 61:4)
    - Questionnaires- Disabled Action Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 61:5)
    - Questionnaires- League of Women Voters, 1999 (Box-folder 61:6)
    - Questionnaires- Make Women Count, 1999 (Box-folder 61:7)
    - Questionnaires- National Organization for Women, 1999 (Box-folder 61:8)
    - Questionnaires- National Rifle Association, 1999 (Box-folder 61:9)
    - Questionnaires- National Right to Work Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 61:10)
    - Questionnaires- Newspapers, 1999 (Box-folder 61:11)
    - Questionnaires- Not Returned, 1999 (Box-folder 61:12)
    - Questionnaires- Sierra Club/Clean Water Action/Campaign Virginia (Joint), 1999 (Box-folder 61:13)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Affiliate of the National Abortion and Reproductive Rights Action League (NARAL), 1999 (Box-folder 61:14)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Education Association, 1999 (Box-folder 61:15)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Foundation for Research and Economic Education, 1999 (Box-folder 61:16)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Human Services Action Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 61:17)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Medical Political Action Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 62:1)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Trial Lawyers Political Action Committee, 1999 (Box-folder 62:2)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Women's Network, 1999 (Box-folder 62:3)
    - Questionnaires- Virginia Women's Political Caucus, 1999 (Box-folder 62:4)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians Against Handgun Violence, 1999 (Box-folder 62:5)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians for Justice, 1999 (Box-folder 62:6)
    - Questionnaires- Virginians for the Arts, 1999 (Box-folder 62:7)
    - Staff- Karen Waters, 2000 (Box-folder 62:8)
    - Steering Committee, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 62:9)
    - Supporters- Artists for Couric, 1999 (Box-folder 62:10)
    - Supporters- Butch Davies Letter, 1999 (Box-folder 62:11)
    - Supporters- Newcomers for Couric, 1999 (Box-folder 62:12)
    - Supporters- Police, 1999 (Box-folder 62:13)
    - Supporters- Republicans and Independents for Couric, 1999 (Box-folder 62:14)
    - Supporters- Larry J. Sabato, 1999 (Box-folder 62:15)
    - Supporters- Teachers for Couric, 1999 (Box-folder 62:16)
    - Supporters- Testimonials, 1999 (Box-folder 62:17)
    - Supporters- University of Virginia Faculty Letter, 1999 (Box-folder 62:18)
  - Subseries C: Lieutenant Governor Campaign
    - Administrative- Josh Darden, 2000 (Box-folder 63:1)
    - Administrative- Al Dwoskin, 2000 (Box-folder 63:2)
    - Administrative- Legal- Til Hazel, 2000 (Box-folder 63:3)
    - Administrative- Morse Speechwriting, 2000 (Box-folder 63:4)
    - Administrative- Planning- Custom Campaigns, 2000 (Box-folder 63:5)
    - Administrative- Staff and Volunteers, 2000 (Box-folder 63:6)
    - Don't Stop Thinking About Tomorrow Political Action Committee, 2000 (Box-folder 63:7)
    - Friends of Emily Couric Contributions, 2000 (Box-folder 63:8)
    - Friends of Emily Couric Letter to Contributors, 2000 (Box-folder 63:9)
    - Friends of Emily Couric- Steering Committee, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 63:10)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Bennett/Virginia Beach Reception, 2000 (Box-folder 63:11)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Democratic Convention, 2000 (Box-folder 63:12)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Hampton Roads Beach Breakfast, 2000 (Box-folder 63:13)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Jefferson- Jackson Day Dinner, 2000 (Box-folder 63:14)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Macaulay Meet and Greet, 2000 (Box-folder 63:15)
    - Fundraisers and Events - Raschke/Richmond Fundraising Reception 2000 (Box-folder 63:16)
    - Fundraisers and Events- Women's Democratic Caucus- Women's Health Care Event, 2000 (Box-folder 63:17)
    - Media- A-B Data Direct Marketing Consultants, 2000 (Box-folder 63:18)
    - Media- Campaign Information, 2000 (Box-folder 63:19)
    - Media- Congressional Races 2000, 2000 (Box-folder 64:1)
    - Media- July 20th Announcement, 2000 (Box-folder 64:2)
    - Media- Master Press Packet, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 64:3)
    - News clippings, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 64:4)
    - Notebook- General, 2000 (Box-folder 64:5)
    - Political Figures- Roy Barnes- Georgia Governor, 1999 (Box-folder 64:6)
    - Political Figures- David Bowers- Mayor of Richmond, 2000 (Box-folder 64:7)
    - Political Figures- Tim Kaine- State of the City Address, 2000 (Box-folder 64:8)
    - Political Figures- Donald McEachin- Democrat for Attorney General, 2000 (Box-folder 64:9)
    - Political Figures- Republican Nominees, 2000 (Box-folder 64:10)
    - Political Figures- Kathleen Kennedy Townsend- Maryland Lieutenant Governor, 2000 (Box-folder 64:11)
    - Supporter Cards- Emailed/Faxed, 2000 July (Box-folder 64:12)
    - Supporter Cards- Legislators, 2000 July (Box-folder 64:13)
    - Supporter Cards- Requests For, 2000 (Box-folder 64:14)
  - Series III: Administrative Files
    - Conflicts of Interest, 1996 January 9 (Box-folder 64:15)
    - Democratic Party Fundraising, 2001 (Box-folder 64:16)
    - Doorplate and Room Number, n.d. (Box-folder 64:17)
    - Events- Baseball Fundraiser, 1996 (Box-folder 64:18)
    - Events- Boone's Mill Apple Festival, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 64:19)
    - Events- Democratic Caucus Brunch/Fundraiser, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 65:1)
    - Events- Hoover Days, 1996, 2000 (Box-folder 65:2)
    - Events- Make a Difference Day, 2000 (Box-folder 65:3)
    - Events- Senate Caucus, 1991, 1995 (Box-folder 65:4)
    - Events- Senate Caucus, 1996 (Box-folder 65:5)
    - Events- Senate Caucus, 1997-1998, n.d. (Box-folder 65:6)
    - Events- Southern Women in Public Service Convention- Reception, 2000 (Box-folder 65:7)
    - Events- Teachers Reception, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 65:8)
    - Financial- IRS Reporting Requirements, 2000 (Box-folder 65:9)
    - Financial- Leave and Pay, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 65:10)
    - Financial- Leave and Pay, 1997 (Box-folder 65:11)
    - Financial- Leave and Pay, 1999 (Box-folder 65:12)
    - Financial- Leave and Pay, 1999 (Box-folder 66:1)
    - Financial- Leave and Pay, 2000 (Box-folder 66:2)
    - Financial- Lobbyist Disclosure Statements, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 66:3)
    - Financial- Office Expense Accounting, 2000 (Box-folder 66:4)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Notebooks, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 66:5)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Office Supplies and Mailings, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 66:6)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Phone Service, 1996 (Box-folder 66:7)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Phone Service, 1997 (Box-folder 66:8)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Phone Service, 1998 (Box-folder 66:9)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Phone Service, 1999 (Box-folder 67:1)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Phone Service, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 67:2)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Receipts, General, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 67:3)
    - Financial- Office Expenses- Receipts, General, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 67:4)
    - Financial- Salary and Benefits, 1995 (Box-folder 67:5)
    - Financial- Statements of Economic Interest, 1997-2001, n.d. (Box-folder 67:6)
    - Financial- Taxes, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 67:7)
    - Media- 1999 Session Newsletter, 1998-1999, n.d. (Box-folder 67:8)
    - Media- Richmond Times Dispatch Editorial, 1999, n.d. (Box-folder 67:9)
    - Media- Voters for Choice TV Spot, 2000 (Box-folder 68:1)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1994, 1995, n.d. (Box-folder 68:2)
    - News clippings and Obituary, 1996, 2001 (Box-folder 68:3)
    - Oath of Office, 1996 (Box-folder 68:4)
    - Office Business Plan, n.d. (Box-folder 68:5)
    - Piedmont Council of the Art Award, 2000, October 20 (Box-folder 68:6)
    - Politicians- John Boyd for Congress, 2000 (Box-folder 68:7)
    - Politicians-Donal Day, 1999 (Box-folder 68:8)
    - Politicians- Virgil Goode, 1995-1996, 1998 (Box-folder 68:9)
    - Politicians- L.F. Payne, 1996-1997, n.d. (Box-folder 68:10)
    - Politicians- Dr. Warren A Stewart- Direct Mail Piece, 2000 (Box-folder 68:11)
    - Politicians- Virginia Officials, 1993-1995, n.d. (Box-folder 68:12)
    - Politicians- Jody Wagner for Congress, 2000 (Box-folder 68:13)
    - Politicians- Mark Warner for Senate, 1996 (Box-folder 68:14)
    - Politicians- Doug Wilder, 2000 (Box-folder 68:15)
    - Reports from Richmond, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 68:16)
    - State Politics- Letter from Irene [Thomaidis], 1996 (Box-folder 68:17)
    - Steering Committee Notes, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 68:18)
    - Virginia Public Access Project, 2000 (Box-folder 68:19)
    - Women and Politics, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 68:20)
    - Women's Campaign Fund, 1996, n.d. (Box-folder 68:21)
    - Women's Center Pioneer Award, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 68:22)
    - Writing- Correspondence Concerning, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 68:23)
    - Yorktown High School Class of 1965- Reunions, 1985, 1990, 1995 (Box-folder 68:24)
- Series IV: Constituent Mail
  - Correspondence- Constituents A- Alston, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 69:1)
  - Correspondence- Constituents Altman- Ayers, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 69:2)
  - Correspondence- Constituents Babcock- Benson, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 69:3)
  - Correspondence- Constituents Berke- Booth, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 69:4)